[Music]
[Música]
Very good, how are you my lordship, how
muy buenas qué tal mi señoría cómo
are you? Well, today I wasn't thinking of making any
estáis bueno hoy no pensaba hacer ningún
videos on the subject, what's happening in the
vídeo sobre el tema lo que pasa en el
broth? This slide today is splendid.
caldo está corredera hoy está espléndida
First of all, I have to
en primer lugar tengo que darle las
thank this follower, Anabel, who
gracias a esta seguidora anabel que me
sent me an audio that is going to leave us
ha mandado un audio que nos va a dejar
indifferent. I can't watch in the afternoons,
indiferente yo que por las tardes no
save me completely, maybe I'll take
puedo ver sálvame entero si acaso le
a look to see what's going on, but I ca
echo un vistazo para ver qué pasa pero
n't see everything because I'm here
todo no lo puedo ver porque estoy aquí
doing things, no, but she sent me this audio
haciendo cosas no pero manda este audio
that is going to leave us indifferent.
que nos va a dejar indiferente
Look, I'm a follower of yours. This afternoon,
mira soy una seguidora tuya esta tarde
on the subject of Kiko Rivera, about the son
sobre el tema de kiko rivera del hijo
who made his first communion, a guest
que ha hecho la comunión un invitado
only capable of criticizing the slide, very
solo capaz de criticar la corredera muy
chemical, she says that the children should be
química ella dice que a los niños hay
left aside, their
que dejarlos aparte
red eyes because Anabel appears,
los ojos rojos porque aparece anabel
fantastic, typical of Carlota,
fantástico típico de carlota que os
see you later. I saw before starting with the
veáis vi antes de comenzar con el tema
main topic of this video, okay, today
principal de este vídeo vale que hoy
I hope it is shorter than usual, I
espero que sea más cortito de lo normal
don't want to leave a couple of things out,
no quiero dejarme un par de cosas en el
okay, first of all, a little bit
tintero vale en primer lugar un poquito
before I start recording this video, not
antes de comenzar a grabar este vídeo no
looking for  little thing a couple of notes and
buscando cosilla un par de apuntes y
such I came across this news that was
demás me encontraba con esta noticia que
published today right now 5 years ago
se publica hoy hace ahora mismo 5 ahora
not from the newspaper la razón public this
no del periódico la razón pública esta
news and I don't know the
noticia y no sé sigue habiendo el
headline is still there no but especially seeing the
titular no pero sobre todo viendo el
content it's going to seem very familiar to you I do
contenido os va a resultar muy familiar
n't know
no sé a mí me ha llamado mucho la
this news really caught my attention you can read it
atención esta noticia la podéis leer
okay look for it or stop in the video read it
vale buscarla o parar en el vídeo leerla
yourselves and tell me if the
ustedes mismos y decirme si os suena el
content of this news sounds familiar to you ok from the
contenido de esta noticia ok de el
newspaper la razón I don't care okay I don't care
periódico la razón a mí me da igual vale
at all if
a mí me da exactamente igual que se
news is published based on my videos I don't care at
saquen noticias a raíz de mis vídeos me
all but man I
da completamente igual pero hombre yo
think that a minimum no a minimum of good
creo que un mínimo no un mínimo de buena
practice would be to cite the valuable source
praxis sería citar la fuente valiosa
because in the end the one who spent
porque al final el que se pegó el
Friday and Saturday swallowing a
viernes y el sábado tragándose una
week of sálvame de marzo
semana de sálvame de marzo
was me I don't mind if you publish
fui yo no me importa que saquéis
news and
noticias y que cojáis el guión entero de
take the entire script of my videos if you want but man at least a citation wouldn't hurt because in the end what I know is not work I also want to remind you that we have released a mobile application so that you can be on it all day long in  our
estar todo el día cotidiano en nuestro
forum in the forum of my kids
foro en el foro de mi chavalería
dot com you can be there from your computer
puntocom podéis estar desde el ordenador
if you want my kids dot com is an
si queréis me chavalería punto com es un
internet portal that has forums
portal de internet que tiene foros
news a humor magazine a store it
noticias una revista de humor una tienda
has everything okay but what you're
tiene de todo vale pero ustedes lo que
going to like the most is obviously the forum
más va a gustar evidentemente es el foro
so you don't throw away okay there are all kinds of
para que no tiréis vale hay todo tipo de
political topics to the PSE or YouTube the
temas políticas al pse o de youtube el
topic Rocío Carrasco survivors the
tema rocío carrasco supervivientes la
temptation is whatever you want okay and to make it
tentación es lo que queráis vale y para
more comfortable for me sir Hería and
que sea más cómodo para mí señor hería y
for me kids well we have designed
para mí chavalería pues hemos diseñado
a totally free application okay so that it is
una aplicación totalmente gratuita vale
not complicated and I leave it in
que para que no complique y lo dejo en
the description the link in the description you
la descripción el link en la descripción
have a link it gives it and it is installed for
tenéis un link le da un y se instala
free easy so that writer
gratis facilito para que escritor día
everyday you can do it because here with the
cotidiano lo podéis que a mí acá con la
host if you are studying life
[__] si es que os estudiando la vida
well also you can send me through this through
bueno además me podéis mandar por este
this forum through the forum you
por este foro a través del foro me
can send me information that I am
podéis mandar información que yo estoy
avoiding all the time when I can I am
por evitando todo el tiempo cuando puedo
not you have blown up my email because
no soy me habéis petado el email porque
you have burned a lot
habéis ardido muchísimo
and it is not for less with  a tweet I bet
y no es para menos con un tuit apuesto
Carlota Corredera broth tiña corredera
carlota corredera caldo tiña corredera
the tweet would be this one in particular it's not
el tuit sería este en concreto no es
simply that it doesn't say any words it
simplemente no dice ninguna palabra
simply puts a screenshot in which she
simplemente pone una captura en la que
is calling well she is no longer the
está convocando bueno ya no es la
organizer but she is helping to
organizadora pero está ayudando a
spread the word she is calling people
difundir nos está convocando a la gente
to a rally in favor of a
a una concentración a favor una
rally in front of the Ministry of
concentración ante el ministerio de
Justice this of swallowing or in other words a
justicia esto de tragar o sea una
rally to ask for the pardon of
concentración para pedir el indulto de
Juana Rivas it is that I really do understand
juana rivas es que realmente sí entiendo
card there is no nonsense but I don't understand why
card hay quitó el rollo pero no entiendo
you are surprised by anything about Carlota
que os sorprendan nada de carlota
Corredera it is the first time that Carlota
corredera es la primera vez que carlota
Corredera has spoken publicly
corredera se ha pronunciado públicamente
in favor of the pardon to Wanna Arriba she already
a favor del indulto a wanna arriba ya lo
did it on one occasion in fact I saw it
hizo en una ocasión de hecho lo vi hace
recently in the tweet of lapidar I put it
poco en el tuit de lapidar yo lo pongo
here okay I think
por aquí vale creo que ha sido
the testimony that you have
impresionante el testimonio que habéis
obtained has been impressive and with Juan's interview
conseguido y con la entrevista de juan
above all pressured the mind
arriba presionante sobre todo la mente
this is my opinion it is not that of the program
esta es mi opinión no es la del programa
I have believed and believed Juana man of
yo he creído y creído juana hombre por
course I believe who is going to believe
supuesto que creo a quién va a creer a
justice Carlota al well of
la justicia carlota al bueno por
course Juana because she has told it is
supuesto a juana porque ha contado es
true  I think the
cierto creo que hay que solucionaría la
situation needs to be resolved, hers and all other
situación la de ella y la de todas las
women's situations are comfortable,
mujeres están comodidades
the situation needs to be resolved. To
hay que solucionar la situación para
put it into context in case there's
poner un poco en contexto por si hay
anyone in Spain who still doesn't know
alguien en españa que todavía no sepa
about the case of Juana Riva. She's a woman
sobre el caso de juana riva es una mujer
who has been convicted of kidnapping
que ha sido condenada por secuestrar a
her children. She's been convicted of two
sus hijos ha sido condenada por dos
counts of child abduction. She's
delitos de sustracción de menores
currently being sentenced after a
actualmente está condenada después de
reduced sentence because the first sentence was
rebajar la sentencia porque primero fue
five years. Okay, currently
de cinco años vale actualmente está
the sentence has been reduced to two and a half years
rebajada la condena a dos años y medio
in prison to six years of removal from
de cárcel a seis años de retirada de la
custody of her children and the payment of
custodia de sus hijos y al pago de una
compensation, which has also been reduced
indemnización que también está rebajada
compared to the first instance.
en comparación con la primera instancia
Not from twelve thousand euros, before, they sentenced her
no de doce mil euros ante la condenaron
to 30,000, but it's been reduced to twelve thousand,
a 30.000 pero se han rebajado a doce mil
twelve thousand euros for moral and
doce mil euros por daños morales y
material damages caused to the father of the
materiales causados al padre de los
minors, very little. There are thirty thousand
menores poquísimos haya treinta mil
euros, it seems to me that it was fine, twelve thousand
euros me parece que estaba bien doce mil
euros seems very little to me because this
euros me parece poquísimo porque esta
lady, in addition to all the damage not only has
señora además todo el daño no solamente
she done without letting that
que él ha hecho sin dejar ver a ese
father see his children, but she's also
padre a sus hijos sino que además ha
been in all the
estado en todos los medios de
media accusing the father of anything
comunicación acusando al padre de todo
goes, even there are politicians and
vale incluso hay políticos y
presenters and collaborators who have
presentadores y colaboradores que han
compared that man to Jose Breton
comparaba ese hombre con jose bretón
but like
pero como
literally so giving him twelve thousand
literalmente así que ponerle doce mil
euros seems to me that to give himself a
euros me parece que para darse con un
pat on the back the fact that they've already
canto en los dientes el hecho de que la
sentenced her to two and a half years already
hayan condenado ya a dos años y medio ya
seems to me that he should shut his
me parece que debería callarse la
mouth lower his ear
boquita agacha la oreja
the sentence and let's go because it turns out that he
la condena y vámonos pues no resulta ser
dedicates you I saw that this woman as she
que te dedique te vi que esta mujer como
says that she is an abused woman well they
dice que es una mujer maltratada pues
are asking for a pardon she is asking
están pidiendo el indulto está pidiendo
not to go to jail but she is being supported by
no ir a la cárcel pero la está apoyando
collaborating politicians and all the
políticos colaboradores y todas las
feminist elites this is incredible it is already being
élites feministas esto es increíble se
asked that a woman
está pidiendo ya que una mujer por decir
can commit
que es mujer maltratada pueda cometer
any type of crime for saying that she is an abused woman and be
cualquier tipo de delitos y que sea
pardoned also air of Montero and
indultado también aire de montero y de
Montero which is a wonder really
montero que es una maravilla de verdad
although we are going to with the votes
aunque la vayamos a con los votos dentro
soon okay no longer call the
de poco vale ya no vaya a llamar el
government at least that the goal of the
gobierno por lo menos que la meta del
comedy club' or something like that
club de la comedia' o algo de eso que la
keep her because I want to continue seeing
mantengan porque yo quiero seguir viendo
the headlines of Irene Montero Irene
los titulares de irene montero irene
Montero defends Juana Rivas and asks for
montero defiende a juana rivas y pide
feminist justice for her and she has to
justicia feminista para ella y tiene que
feminist justice
la justicia feminista la justicia
feminist justice that a justice in which a
feminista que una justicia en la que la
woman, for being a woman, can commit
mujer por ser mujer pueda ejecutar
any type of crime and not be
cualquier tipo de delito y no se la
condemned because I do not understand it
condene porque yo no lo entiendo
feminist justice, bow to the palate,
justicias feministas agache al paladar
whoever is in charge is here, I am not going to
cualquier que manda es acá no lo voy a
apply it as briefly as possible and you
aplicar lo más resumido posible y usted
and if it is normal that Carlota Corredera
y si es normal que carlota corredera
is participating in calling people together
esté participando en convocar a la gente
and in supporting this lady and in asking for her
y en apoyar a esta señora y en pedir su
pardon after what she is doing
indulto después de la que está liando
with Antonio Avilés that this woman
con antonio avilés que esta mujer
Carlota Corredera seems to be going
carlota corredera parece ser que va en
against justice what
contra de la justicia lo que digan los
the judges say few notes Corredera you correct them because she already has the absolute truth, I mean, what the [ __ ] will there be a guy about the law what the [ __ ] do they know? Well, Carlota Corredera will know what a feminist I [ __ ] on ten even if she keeps
feminista me cago en diez aunque luego
quiet about other cases but well, back
se calle con otros casos pero bueno allá
in 2008-2009 this lady who
por el año 2008-2009 esta señora que
had a partner with whom she had been together for 15
tenía una pareja con la que se lleva 15
years and a child in common at a
años y un hijo en común en un momento
specific moment when she came home late or something like that,
puntual que llega a su casa tarde o algo
a big argument started
por el estilo empieza una gran discusión
and  It seems that the two come to blows,
y se ve que los dos llegan a las manos
both he and she denounce
tanto él como ella se denuncian
each other, what happens is that the man, very badly
mutuamente lo que pasa es que el muy mal
advised by his lawyer, withdraws the
aconsejado por su abogado retira la
complaint that he filed against her because the
denuncia que le pone a ella porque el
lawyer recommended it so that there would not be
abogado se lo recomienda para que no
any retaliation later, something would
haya después ninguna represalia algo le
prevent her from seeing her children, whatever it is, she
impida ver a sus hijos lo que sea ella
maintains the complaint, he condemns him
mantiene la denuncia ya él lo condena
for abuse, they condemn him for abuse
por maltrato lo condenan por maltrato a
despite the fact that the
pesar de que luego han salido los
medical reports have later come out and it turns out that he
informes médicos y resulta ser que él
had a lot of
tenía mucho
physical damage, and with that we have not even
daño físico que con eso ni siquiera
begun the thing, right after
hemos empezado la cosa que justo después
the conviction, right after this
de la condena justo después de que este
man was convicted, they reconciled, she
hombre lo condenen se reconcilia ella
returned to him in 2012 I think it was, they
vuelve con él en 2012 creo que fue se
went to live in Italy because they are from
van a vivir a italia porque ellas de
Granada and he is from Italy, they went to
granadas y él es de italia se van a
live in Italy, they made their life there, they have
vivir a italia hacen su vida allí tienen
another child and in Padrón, the
otro hijo y en padrón haga llegue al
child arrives, the children go to school and
niño los niños van hacia el colegio y de
suddenly for some reason she decides in
repente por algún motivo ella decide en
2016 to take a flight, she comes to
2016 cogerse un vuelo se viene para
Granada telling the man that she is going to
granada diciéndole al hombre que va a
visit her family and that she will return with
visitar a su familia y que volverá con
the children, she will not return, she sent him an
los niños no vuelve más le mandó un
email and tells him that she is staying in Granada
email y le dice que se queda en granada
that she loves us and more to Italy and that if
que nos quiere y más a italia y que si
he wants her to come see him whenever she
él quiere que venga a verlo cuando
wants a couple of months after this
quiera un par de meses después de esto
she goes and files another complaint for
ella coge y le planta otra denuncia por
abuse that seeing as how the first time
maltrato que viendo que la primera vez
went well the master letter could have been I'll
salió bien podido la carta maestra te
report you for abuse and I'll keep
denuncio por maltrato y me quedo yo con
the children this seems to me to be what we have
los niños es que esto a mí me parece lo
talked about many times using
que hemos hablado muchas veces utilizar
the complaints as a weapon against the man
las denuncias como arma contra el hombre
the thing is that on this occasion not only
la cosa que en esta ocasión no solamente
the judge does not agree with her but
el juez no le da la razón sino que
also makes reference to the fact that at the time
además hace referencia a que en su día
the other sentence could have and should have been
la otra condena se pudo y se tuvo que
fought because everything pointed to
haber peleado porque todo apuntaba
sexist abuse it was a fight between the
maltrato machista era una pelea entre
two in which the two got into a fight
los dos en la que los dos se metieron
here we can see some extracts of
manos aquí podemos ver unos extractos de
the sentence taken from one of the
la sentencia que sacado de uno de los
videos of a straight white guy that I
vídeos de un tío blanco hetero que os
recommend you watch I will leave it in the
recomiendo que lo veáis lo dejaré en la
description on may 18 2016
descripción el 18 de mayo de 2016
juana rivas moved to granada with
juana rivas se trasladó a granada con
the two minors stating that she was
los dos menores manifestando que lo
doing it to visit family and
hacía para visitar a la familia y
showing intention of returning again
mostrando intención de volver nuevamente
in a month to the family residence
en un mes a la residencia familiar
arrived at the return date she did not do it she
llegada a la fecha de vuelta no lo hizo
said nothing and  On July 12, 2016, she
dijo que nada y el 12 de julio de 2016
filed a complaint for abuse
interpuso una denuncia por malos tratos
against Francesco in the Granada Court of
contra francesco en el juzgado de
Violence 2, stating
violencia 2 de granadas manifestando
beforehand to Elche that she was sick and
antes a elche que se hallaba enferma y
would not return on the scheduled date,
no iba a volver en la fecha prevista
when in reality she had made the
cuando en realidad había adoptado la
decision not to return with her two
decisión de no retornar con los dos
children here, the strong ones, and to keep them with
hijos acá los fuertes y mantenerlos con
her in Granada. The
ella en granada- no es creíble la
certainty of the facts contained in this
certeza de los hechos contenidos en esta
complaint is not credible because no court has
denuncia porque ningún juzgado ha
declared the veracity of the same
declarado la veracidad de los mismos
because it is filed at a
porque la misma se interpone en un
time in which
tiempo en el que ya se ha dado inicio a
that set of actions carried
ese conjunto de actuaciones llevados a
out by the accused to consolidate her
cabo por la acusada para consolidar su
decision not to return and not to hand over
decisión de no volver y no entregar a
the children has already begun. In
los niños
other words, she is also proposing
o sea ella la demás le está proponiendo
to the father that he can come see him whenever he
al padre que puede venir a verlo cuando
wants. There is no fear or
quieras ahí no hay ningún miedo ni
terror or wanting to hide, no,
ningún terror o de querer esconderse no
or that she is afraid that the father will
o que tenga algún miedo de que el padre
approach her or the children. When
se acerca a ella oa los hijos cuando las
complaints for abuse are filed
denuncias por malos tratos se interponen
concurrently with a
de forma coetánea a un proceso de
separation process or due to disputes over
separación o por disputas sobre guarda y
custody or comes, a cautious analysis is required,
custodia o viene se exige un análisis
above all, she has ideas.
cauteloso sobre todo tiene ideas se
past events are recounted that could have been
relatan hechos pasados que se pudieron
reported before, in addition they emphasize
denunciar antes además hacen hincapié en
that she is not able to recount well and
que ella no es capaz de relatar bien y
specifically any event that could be
concretamente ningún hecho que pueda ser
abuse during all those years of
de maltrato durante todos esos años de
reconciliation in which they were captured with him, in
reconciliación en los captados con él de
fact she even says that the eldest son
hecho incluso dice que el hijo mayor
also suffered abuse but still
también sufrió malos tratos pero igual
according to the examination by experts to the child and
la según examen los expertos al niño y
such and they conclude that there is nothing, let's
tal y concluyen que no hay nada vamos
know is the protective effect that
sabido es el efecto tuitivo que
the public authorities deploy with
despliegan los poderes públicos con
respect to people affected by
respecto a las personas afectadas por
abuse, one of which is to
malos tratos uno de los cuales es
remove minors from the abuser and
apartar a los menores del maltratador y
logically with that perspective it is not
lógicamente con esa perspectiva no es
strange as practice shows that in
extraño como muestra la práctica que en
some cases this route is used as a
algunos casos se recurre a esta vía como
means of obtaining procedural advantages
medio de obtener ventajas procesales
white and
blanco y en
since the judge could not have been
ya que el juez no ha podido ser más
clearer here after this she joins
claro aquí después de esto ella se une a
the entire feminist media elite and
toda la élite feminista mediática y
begins to carry out a campaign as if she
empieza a realizar una campaña como si
were some kind of infinite victim of abuse
fuera una especie de víctima de maltrato
and also as a kind of
infinita y además como una especie de
heroine who is doing is
heroína que lo que está haciendo es
protecting her children from a terrible
proteger a sus hijos de un terrible
monster, furthermore during all these
monstruo además durante todos estos
months that she is appearing in the media
meses que está apareciendo en los medios
she recounts perfectly that she knows that she has to
ella relata perfectamente que sabe que
hand over  to your children but you are
tiene que entregar a sus hijos pero que
not going to do it to you nobody told you
no lo va a hacer a usted nadie le dijo
that you could commit a crime because you
que usted podía cometer un delito porque
were doing I am going to be committing
estaba haciendo voy a estar cometiendo
a crime
un delito
no faith that I know increased to three
ninguna fe que yo sepa aumentado a tres
or four lawyers none of those
o cuatro abogadas ninguna de esas
lawyers tell you that you could be
abogadas le digo a usted que podría
committing a crime you were
estar cometiendo un delito
warned that you could be
se le advirtió que podría usted estar
committing a crime there
cometiendo un delito
was a time when they told me that I
hubo un momento que a mí me dijeron que
could have reprisals at the level of
podía tener represalias de a nivel de
justice but I did not imagine that
justicia pero yo no imaginaba que ni
much less well yes with years of prison
mucho menos pues sí con años de cárcel
keep the report and shine or day I do not
guardar el atestado y luce o día yo no
know what
sé qué
because I believe that a lawyer first of all
porque yo creo que un abogado primero
usually says is listen be careful
que suele decir es oiga usted cuidado
for what you are doing that this is
por lo que está haciendo que esto está
classified as a crime and you spoke to me
tipificado como delito y me habló usted
about three to four lawyers none of them
de tres a cuatro abogados que ninguno le
tell you where the crime I no longer know how to say
dice donde el delito yo ya no sé decir
what kind of lawyer could you or is it that
qué clase de abogada podría usted o es
you do
que usted me
not want to accept that they already warned you
no quiere aceptar que que le advirtieron
of what was happening
ya de lo que pasaba
well you surprise me that four
bien usted me extraña que cuatro
lawyers that you have asked as if you
abogados que usted ha pedido como que
went to them say very well all this
acudía a ellos digan muy bien todo esto
about the resources is very well the
de los recursos está muy bien el
constitutional court everything
tribunal constitucional todo lo que
you want but between 12 to the children
usted quiera pero entre 12 a los niños
because you could be committing a crime
porque puede estar cometiendo un delito
nobody  He said that the
nadie le dijo eso
main thing they didn't tell me that I could face
principal no me dijeron que podía tener
legal retaliation that I could have
represalia a nivel legal que podía tener
difficulties but for me it was superior
dificultades pero para mí era superior
in the protection of my son and being able to what I
en la protección a mi hijo y poder lo
was trying to do was regulate
que intentaba era regular
again and the lawyers had a good time
otra vez y lo pasaron bien los abogados
and
y
on July 11, 2017 the court of
el 11 de julio de 2017 el juzgado de
first instance number 3 of Granada
primera instancia número 3 de granada
issued an order of forced execution because the
dictó auto de ejecución forzosa pues la
accused had not complied with the ruling of the
acusada no había cumplido el fallo de la
sentence before said, that is to say the man
sentencia ante dicha es decir el hombre
had her reporting in Italy and the
la tuvo denunciando en italia y la
Italian justice asks the Spanish one,
justicia de italia le pide a la de
clinging to the
españa' agarrándose al convenio de la
Hague Convention that immediately that lady has to
haya que inmediatamente esa señora tiene
return the children to the father and
que devolver a los hijos al padre y la
required her to immediately comply with the
requirió al inmediato cumplimiento del
same, giving her a period of three
mismo confiriéndole un plazo de tres
days to deliver the
días para que entregase a los menores
unattended minors the previous requirement the
desatendido el anterior requerimiento el
same court issued a resolution on
mismo juzgado dictó resolución el 24 de
July 24, 2017 by which it combined the
julio de 2017 por la que combinaba a la
immediate delivery on July 26 at
entrega inmediata el 26 de julio a las
four thirty at the family meeting point
cuatro y media en el punto de encuentro
located on Sevilla street
familiar ubicado en la calle sevilla
number one in this city, traveling
número uno de esta ciudad desplazándose
to the same the father of the children
hasta el mismo el padre de los niños
together with the  Italian consular authority
junto a la autoridad consular de italia
and a police force without the
y una dotación policial sin que la
accused appearing or giving
acusada se presentará ni diera
an explanation for her absence, let's say it did
explicación sobre su inasistencia vamos
n't feel like it, she hands over the
que no le salió del potorro entrega los
children, after this what she has done has
niños después de esto lo que ha hecho
even been hiding and it is even
incluso ha sido esconderse e incluso se
said that she has
dice que ha tenido
hidden them without taking them to school and
escondido sin llevarlo al colegio y
so on and there are people who are asking for her to be
demás y hay gente que está pidiendo que
pardoned, so look at the
se la indulte o sea que fijaros en la
move as it is, they do not report
movida como es no se denuncian
each other when they fight
mutuamente cuando se pelean
obviously she wins because she
evidentemente sale ganando ella porque
is a woman and because he also withdraws
es una mujer y porque además él retira
the complaint despite having had more
la denuncia a pesar de haber tenido más
injuries than her, they reconcile during
lesiones que ella se reconcilian durante
all those years they reconcile and she
todos esos años que se reconcilian y se
goes to Italy with him far from being terrified
va a italia con él lejos de tener terror
by this monster and another child and lives
por este monstruo y en otro hijo y vive
fully with him but when she gets
plenamente con él pero cuando se le
crossed she comes to Spain, brings
cruza el cable se viene a españa se trae
the children by deceiving the father and does not feel like
a los niños engañando al padre y no le
handing them over she does not care about
sale del pomelo entregarlo se la sudan
the judges and she does not care about the
los jueces y se la suda la justicia
Spanish justice system, the Italian justice system does not care about
española la justicia italiana se la suda
anything she goes and says I'll file another
todo ella coge y dice yo te pongo otra
complaint for abuse, the
denuncia por maltrato me salió bien la
first one went well, really stupid monkey, we're leaving,
primera bien boba mono que nos vamos
continue, the children are not there, they stay  here the
siga no está los niños se quedan aquí la
exit shot in the foot the sentence
salida del tiro por la culata la condena
and on top of that presenters like Carlota
y encima presentadores como carlota
collaborators journalists and even
colaboradores periodistas e incluso
government officials are asking for a
cargos del gobierno le están pidiendo el
pardon incredible we could be here
indulto increíble podríamos estar aquí
three hours setting an example of people
tres horas poniendo ejemplo de la gente
in the government and all the
del gobierno y de todos los personajes
public figures who have supported this case but what
públicos que han apoyado este caso pero
surprises me for example this one from
a mí me sorprende por ejemplo este de
Alberto to
alberto a
Juana Rivas has been sentenced to 5 years
juana rivas ha sido condenada a 5 años
in prison for trying to protect her
de cárcel por intentar proteger a sus
children from an abuser a
hijos de un maltratador una justicia
patriarchal justice deeply unjust Juana
patriarcal profundamente injusta juana
Rivas deserves a pardon from the government and
rivas merece el indulto del gobierno y
Alberto Garzón goes even further he
alberto garzón va todavía más allá se
starts retweeting tweets like this
pone a retuitear tweets como este
throwing [ __ ] and insulting the judge a
tirándole [__] e insultando al juez un
state official who we pay
cargo del estado al que le pagamos
insulting a judge okay he is
insultando a un juez vale está
enjoying retweeting a tweet where
disfrutando retuiteando tuit donde se le
the judge is enjoying himself a person
está disfrutando al juez a una persona
who is doing his job with all the
que está haciendo su trabajo con todo el
rigor in the world complying with the law and
rigor del mundo cumpliendo la ley y en
based on some knowledge and
base a unos conocimientos y a unos
studies that he has I am going to add this
estudios que tiene voy a añadir este
tweet from my friend Carlos Salgado who you already
tuit de mi amigo carlos salgado que ya
know is a man that I interviewed
sabéis que es un hombre que entreviste
on my channel is a man who has
en mi canal es un hombre que tienen a su
kidnapped life alberto garzón
vida secuestrada alberto garzón esta
we took this photo in blanes when
foto nos lo hicimos en blanes cuando
you came for the
viniste para la campaña de las
2015 municipal election campaign the girl you see in
municipales de 2015 la niña que ves en
the photo is my daughter kidnapped by her
la foto es mi hija secuestrada por su
mother in kyrgyzstan it's a shame that you
madre en kirguistán es una pena que
ask for a pardon for a kidnapper
pidas el indulto para una secuestradora
and not help me get my daughter back
y no me ayudes a recuperar a mi hija
as a white guy from teno says in
como bien dice un tío blanco de teno en
his video that shows carlos's capture it
su vídeo que saca la captura de carlos
hurts me a lot to tell you this because you
me duele mucho decirte esto porque tú
know that I'm here for whatever
sabe que aquí me tiene para lo que sea
but helping you who are a
pero es que ayudarte a ti que eres un
man doesn't get votes this is incredible
hombre no da votos esto es increíble
two months listening to carlota corredera
dos meses escuchando a carlota corredera
and all her elite asking for jail time for
y a toda su elite pidiendo cárcel para
antonio dhabi that justice be done that
antonio dhabi que se haga justicia que
justice has made a mistake that they have to
la justicia se ha equivocado que tienen
judge him and how can they not condemn him
que juzgarlo y como no condenarlo la
justice always makes mistakes when
justicia siempre se equivoca cuando no
the numbers don't add up we are
le salen las cuentas de ellas estamos
talking about that man antonio david
hablando de que ese hombre antonio david
is a monster because he hasn't returned
es un monstruo porque no ha devuelto a
his son when he had to return him and
su hijo cuando lo tuvo que devolver y
now however we ask for a pardon be
ahora sin embargo pedimos el indulto sea
a person who has been more than
una persona que ha sido más que
condemned but more than condemned I mean it's
condenada pero más que condenada o sea
no longer to say  provisionally acquitted no no no
ya no es decir sobreseída provisional no
more than with nothing more than judged a
no no
person that the judges have already seen everything they
persona que ya los jueces han visto todo
had to see before deciding
lo que tenían que ver antes de decidir
her sentence and in fact the one that they have
su condena y de hecho la que la han
imposed on her has been too lenient well
puesto han sido demasiado benevolentes
no because it is a woman who claims to
pues no pues como es una mujer que dice
be a victim of abuse these people
ser víctima de maltrato de un esta gente
can commit all the crimes they
pueden cometer todos los delitos que
want listen patriarchal justice is not like that here
quieran oye justicia patriarcal aquí no
women should be allowed to
es así hay que dejar a las mujeres que
do whatever the hell they want they
hagan lo que les salga del porno ya
are already asking for one thing Antonio David
están pidiendo una cosa antonio david
when there is no evidence there is no evidence that
cuando no hay pruebas no hay pruebas de
Antonio had already done all those
que antonio había ya hecho todas esas
things of which he accuses her and now we are
cosas de la que la acusa y estamos ahora
according to the judges also with a case
según los jueces además con un caso
change more than judged it is that these people
cambio más que juzgado es que esta gente
have to put into doubt the judges
tienen que poner en duda los jueces
come out of their balls then with Rocío
salen de los [__] luego con rocío
Flores they have it very clear here they are
flores lo tienen muy claro aquí están
asking for a pardon my face would fall
pidiendo el indulto a mí se me caería la
of shame especially after having
cara de vergüenza sobre todo después de
just finished documentary the
recién haber terminado documental los
two months the nonsense the [ __ ] that we have
dos meses las burradas la [__] da que
been hearing for two months that in his
llevamos escuchando dos meses que en su
brand new start asking a woman who
flamante ponerse a pedirle una mujer que
is approved but especially that it
está aprobado pero especialmente que
is proven is that he went through the
esté probado es que haya ido por los
media  of communication saying no
medios de comunicación diciendo que no
that it doesn't come out of the grapefruit hands over the
que no le sale del pomelo entrega a los
children tarnishing the image of a man
niños manchando la imagen de un hombre
being a tremendous damage that man and
siéndolo un daño ese hombre tremendo y
we are asking with all our nerve that
estamos pidiendo con toda la cara que se
he be pardoned for the sentence that he be pardoned for the
le perdone la condena que se le perdonen
crimes he has committed because he
los delitos que haya cometido porque
says he is an abused woman in the
dice ser una mujer maltratada en la
perfect letter is if you realize it
carta perfecta es si os dais cuenta es
would be perfect I mean any woman
que sería perfecto o sea cualquier mujer
suddenly feels like committing any
de repente se le apetece hacer cualquier
crime goes and says that she has done it because she
delito va y dice que lo ha hecho porque
is an abused woman even if
es una mujer maltratada aunque no la
justice does not rule on their side and that they
justicia no les dé la razón y que me
forgive me for my crimes I mean it is
perdonen mis delitos o sea que es
incredible it is incredible it is nonsense and
increíble es increíble es un disparate y
[ __ ] nonsense I wish it were just as
[__] disparate ojalá fuera es igual de
insistent Carlota Corredera with the case
insistente carlota corredera con el caso
for example of Carlota Prado you know
por ejemplo de carlota prado ya sabes
the girls are 'Big Brother'
las chicas están 'gran hermano'
revolution that when they asked you in
revolution que cuando te preguntaron en
La Vanguardia a couple of years ago you did not
la vanguardia hace un par de añitos no
want to get too involved you did not do there is
te quisiste mojar mucho no hiciste hay
a rather evasive answer it is a
una respuesta bastante esquiva es un
subject
tema
that I am not going to go into because those who
en el que no voy a entrar porque quienes
had to speak which are the networks and
tenían que hablar que son las cadenas y
the production company have already spoken to Perón the one
la productora ya han hablado a perón el
of Rocío Carrasco yes  you're going in because
de rocío carrasco si vas a entrar porque
those who have to speak are not
los que tienen que hablar no son
only antonio david rocio carrasco
solamente antonio david rocío carrasco
in that one you go all the way in no even if
en ese te metes hasta el fondo no aunque
the judges speak you go all the way in
hablen los jueces tú te metes hasta el
and now in the one upstream the
fondo y ahora en el de agua arriba lo
same as to get it out is this slide I
mismo que para sacarlo está corredera no
can't get out of there not because I don't have
puedo salirme de ahí no porque no tenga
an opinion but because a
una opinión sino porque un tema
judicialized and very delicate issue for him from
judicializado y muy delicado a él de
good upstream he doesn't lose authority and
bueno arriba no pierde autoridad y
neither here true carlota puts you
tampoco aquí carlota verdadera te mete
where it interests you to put him nothing was happening I don't
donde te interesa meterle no pasaba nada
know why you can't have an opinion about
no sé por qué no puedes opinar lo de
carlos is stopped I consider in the
carlos está parado yo considero en el
case of carlota prado well look it has been
caso de carlota prado pues mira ha sido
a case that the network has not
un caso que la cadena no lo ha
silenced as they are saying out there they have
silenciado como están diciendo por ahí
not covered up but they did
no le han encubierto pero sí que lo
handle it like [ __ ] ass today
gestionaron como el [__] culo hoy de los
we learn from the mistakes no carlota what is it that she
errores aprendemos no carlota qué es lo
has repeated for a long
que ha repetido durante un montón de
time this week that she has been
tiempo en esta semana que ha estado
saying from now on everything that
diciendo a partir de ahora todo lo que
is said in journalism with evidence with
se diga en el periodismo con pruebas con
evidence after 15 years not on
pruebas después de 15 años no en
television what happens carlota from the
televisión que pasa carlota de los
mistakes you learn because you can't
errores se aprende porque no puedes
freely give your opinion about carlota parado  there
opinar libremente de carlota parado ahí
and nothing gentlemen, actually let's see, I
y nada señores yo en realidad a ver me
understand myself a little because it is a [ __ ]
entiendo un poco porque es que un [__]
nonsense it was a [ __ ] nonsense is
disparate era que un [__] disparate es
that we could take now but I'm not
que podríamos [__] ahora pero que no lo
going to do it we could now take every
voy a hacer podríamos [__] ahora cada
phrase that he has said accusing Antonio
frase que ha dicho inculpando antonio
David calling him a victimizer when that man after going through 67 judges have decided not to condemn him no not even play him calling him an aggressor and now you come to me connect is that we could take a lot of phrases that he has said about Antonio David and
ha dicho sobre antonio david y
compare it with this incredible guy who
compararlo con esto tío increíble que lo
is about to sell you hypocrites I
está por vender us hipócritas yo de
really do not support that people insult
verdad no apoyo que la gente insulte a
anyone and nothing but really Carlota
nadie y que nada pero realmente carlota
from desire with all her might every day the
de ganas a pulso cada día la
disapproval of the public and in the end you
desaprobación del público y al final te
are going to load well go load it not
vas a cargar bueno vaya a cargarla no
only save me I think that I am going to
solamente sálvame yo creo que os voy a
load the entire chain with this type of
cargar la cadena entera con este tipo de
nonsense and [ __ ] and expensive
disparates y de chorradas y de de caros
and things that of having no shame I know
y de cosas que de no tener vergüenza sé
I am sincerely of having no shame
estoy sinceramente de no tener vergüenza
five years this anyway sir hurt and
cinco años esto en fin señor hería y
kids  I'm reading your opinion
chavalería estar leyendo vuestra opinión
in the comments box, but I know you're going to
en la caja de comentarios pero sé que
agree with me, so
vais a estar muy de acuerdo conmigo así
don't
que nada os estáis leyendo igualmente no
forget to leave me a line, you're very
olvidéis dejarme un line que estáis muy
active, and I'll see you in the next
activos y nos vemos en el siguiente
video. I'll be waiting.
vídeo estaré pendiente